(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
Should I start making yakbab now?
(It's time to make yakbab for 40 people in the village.)
Wait, I need to calculate.
It's multiplied by six. For thick soy sauce...
Three times six is eighteen.
I'll make it less sweet than yakbab that we're familiar with.
(Adjusting the sweetness with honey,)
(keeping the elders' health in mind)
(It's not easy because the amount is huge.)
(But she's putting her heart into it to make it delicious.)
(Adding cinnamon powder)
(As expected from generous Captain Yum,)
(she whips up the seasoning for a huge batch of yakbab in no time.)
Next is...
(Next up is 40 servings of soaked glutinous rice.)
(Everything goes into the giant rice cooker.)
(And chopped chestnuts and jujubes go in too.)
(Adding plenty without holding back)
(Adding plenty of flavorful pumpkin seeds...)
(and sweet raisins)
(Finally, giving the yakbab seasoning sauce a good stir)
(Pouring it all in generously)
(Packed with healthy ingredients)
It looks delicious.
(Jung Ah's giant batch of yakbab is ready.)
Gosh, my lower back.
(It's also filled with Captain Yum's love.)
The yakbab smells so good, Jung Ah.
(It's turning into delicious yakbab.)
Gosh, nice and golden.
- This side is grilled well.
- It turned out well.
(The wild eel in salt is sizzling to perfection.)
Gosh.
Look at the meat.
(The rich, fatty flesh makes them exclaim automatically.)
It looks meaty.
Gosh, you are working hard.
- It's a work of art.
- Right.
Oh, my.
- Gosh.
- It's really a work of art.
(He can't stop raving about how incredible the wild eel is.)
- Gosh, this is no joke.
- Right.
Look how thick it is.
- Such thickness is rare.
- The smell is amazing.
- It looks delicious.
I think it's ready to eat.
- Go ahead and taste it.
- It looks cooked.
(Golden)
This is no joke.
- It's a work of art.
- Look how thick it is.
(It's absolutely well cooked.)
(He tries a piece of the eel.)
Gosh, it's a work of art.
(It's pure art.)
- Is it cooked?
- It's cooked.
(Clean and delicate with no fishy taste)
It doesn't taste fishy at all. It's incredible.
Try it.
(You Seok also tries a piece of well-cooked wild eel.)
My gosh.
- What?
- Isn't it so good?
Is it good?
- We only added salt to it.
- Of course.
- Gosh, I can't believe it.
- Right?
- We seasoned it only with salt.
- Right.
(The wild eel is bursting with a clean yet deeply rich flavor.)
It's really good. How does it taste like this?
(Gosh, it's hot...)
It's delicious.
It's the ultimate in delicate goodness.
- Gosh.
- It's very savory.
(Golden brown)
It's very good. How is this possible?
(The salt-grilled eel tastes light and savory.)
(Fresh eel caught just today)
(Thanks to the freshness, its taste is clean and deep.)
(Jin Hee is losing himself over it.)
(Pure bliss)
I need to eat that right now.
Immediately...
I need to put it in my mouth.
You have to eat it right away...
It's hard to taste something like this.
Could you put it in my mouth?
(Yoon Seo comes over for Sun Young.)
Thank you. You're the best, Yoon Seo.
- Open up.
- Okay.
Give it to me. I got it.
(Eating with bare hands impatiently)
(How does the grilled wild eel in salt taste?)
It's very meaty.
My goodness.
There's absolutely no smell.
Seriously.
(The meat is wonderfully chewy and savory.)
It's very meaty. It tastes so good.
Should we cook a few in salt and season the rest?
Something like teriyaki sauce or...
- Sun Young.
- Yes?
- Can you make a sauce...
- with soy sauce, - Yes.
- oligosaccharide, - Yes.
cooking wine, and water?
Add some whole garlic, green onions,
and some ginger.
Isn't that too much to memorize?
Can you tell us one ingredient at a time? Wait.
- Send it to her via text.
- Wait. Soy sauce...
Her eyes wavered for a second.
- Just do it roughly like that.
- There's nothing rough about it.
Let's add Cheongyang chili pepper or dried chili to make it spicy.
(Generously adding ingredients that are hard to memorize)
Shall I add some dark soy sauce?
(Including dark soy sauce, Captain Yum's secret kick)
(The eel marinade comes together in no time.)
It's going to taste unique.
(Going straight to the grill)
I'll sprinkle some.
Gosh, look at the color.
(The more sauce she brushes on, the livelier the color becomes.)
- Gosh, it looks beautiful.
- That's good.
It's starting to look like something.
With the sauce, the color got much deeper. It looks tastier.
It's the real deal, isn't it?
(Now it looks more mouthwatering.)
Gosh, doesn't it look incredible?
It's ready to be cut. It's a work of art.
- Jin Hee, it's very...
- Isn't it a work of art?
- You grilled it so well.
- Yes.
- It looks amazing.
- I told you that I was good at it.
Oh, my.
Nothing got messed up.
(Cutting the marinated eel into perfectly sized pieces)
This is incredible.
Gosh, this is insane.
(It's glowing.)
What do you think, art major? Am I plating it well?
It's perfect.
(Coated with sweet and savory sauce and infused with charcoal aroma)
Gosh, it looks much more appetizing...
with the color. Right?
(The grilled wild eel in marinade looks mouthwatering.)
(The wild eel tastes delicious.)
- Aren't we almost done?
- Yes, we are.
Shall we set the table?
(Starting with Sun Young's perfectly simmered napa cabbage soup)
(Seasoning with a final splash of anchovy sauce)
(Straight into bowls before it gets cold)
Gosh, it looks delicious.
(Beautifully plating the main dish, grilled wild eel)
It looks good.
(And refreshing ripened kimchi to make wraps with)
Let's eat.
We're going to eat eel to our heart's content.
(A hearty feast of wild eel barbecue is ready.)
(Golden brown and crispy salt-grilled eel)
(Juicy eel coated with their special sauce)
(A nourishing meal of grilled eel, known as food for restoring energy)
(With Sun Young's refreshing napa cabbage soup)
Gosh, let's eat.
(A healthy, nourishing meal is served.)
- Thank you for the food.
- Well done, everyone.
- Well done.
- My goodness.
(A sip to wash away the fatigue from today's hard work)
(This is refreshing.)
- Gosh.
- The eel...
You worked so hard on grilling the eel.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll start with the one grilled in salt.
(Starting with clean, salt-grilled eel)
(Carefully savoring the rare wild eel)
(Another bite dipped in a lot of sauce)
It's excellent.
(Even the eel master's first choice is eel grilled in salt.)
(Satisfied)
- It's definitely not greasy.
- Not at all.
- There's no hint of fishiness.
- Exactly.
How can it taste this good with nothing but salt?
Right.
The wild eel is...
crispy outside like other grilled eel.
- But the meat inside...
- It's chewy.
It's chewy and very thick.
- It's substantial.
- Like beef, right?
Yes, it's very substantial.
- The texture is...
- Right.
It's incredible.
(Enjoying the eel power)
It's chewy.
(Wild eel that's unbelievably chewy and tasty)
(Top it with shredded ginger for a clean, refreshing bite)
(Next, add a layer of ripened kimchi...)
(and add shredded ginger)
(Tuck it snugly under a blanket of pickled radish)
(Pop it into your mouth for a refreshing flavor)
(Wrap it in perilla leaves for another variation)
(Add some sauce and try it wrapped in lettuce)
(Finish with rinsed ripened kimchi for a refreshing bite)
(The grilled wild eel in salt has won everyone over.)
It's very delicious.
Shall I try the marinated eel?
- It's delicious.
- Do I eat it without anything?
(Switching targets to the marinated eel)
(You Seok also tastes the marinated eel.)
- Gosh.
- What? This?
- The seasoning is perfect.
- Definitely.
(The charcoal aroma gives it a deep flavor.)
- Is it good?
- It's good.
(Following others, Yoon Seo pops a piece into her mouth.)
- It's very chewy.
- It's insane.
- Is the marinated eel good?
- Yes.
- The marinated eel is...
- It's amazing.
You know what?
- Grilling it...
- It's much easier to grill.
- It's so good.
- It's very chewy.
- This much is perfect.
- The marinated eel is amazing.
How many times did you brush on the sauce and grill it?
Four rounds of back and forth. Eight times in total.
It tastes amazing.
- Isn't it good?
- Yes.
If you cook it too long, it'd get crumbly. This is perfectly cooked.
- This...
- It's the right amount of texture.
- It's nice and soft.
- Yes.
- I'm so glad that you did it.
Actually, I'm not a fan of store-bought marinated eel.
But this one...
brings out the texture of the meat inside.
How do I...
This is really amazing.
We caught this one fresh this morning.
So it's...
- What?
- It's so good.
(Copycat)
(He doesn't want to waste even a drop of the delicious sauce.)
It's good.
(A sip of the cabbage soup to cleanse the palate)
(Her eyes light up.)
(The simmered cabbage has a wonderfully soft texture.)
- Start by eating that.
- I just found out.
(You Seok also takes a sip of the soup.)
(Two sips)
- What?
- Isn't the soup delicious?
- The soup is so good.
- Do you like it?
(Slurping in)
- I added all of it.
- To here?
(Humming)
The napa cabbage soup is good.
(Everyone is busy slurping.)
(In love with the napa cabbage soup)
It's really good.
- Is it really good?
- Yes.
It's amazing.
- Shall I try some?
- It's really good.
- Right.
- It's a work of art.
(Taking one more bite)
(My dish is delicious.)
(The refreshing broth goes perfectly with the grilled wild eel.)
(After cleansing her palate, she focuses on the wild eel again.)
(The wild eel is healthy and tasty.)
(The long, exhausting day’s fatigue)
(It's wiped away in one shot by this ultimate stamina food.)
(There's another person who's hooked on wild eel.)
(He's eating,)
(eating,)
(and eating again.)
Honestly, I've never been a huge fan of eel.
- You don't like eels that much?
- No.
(But he's getting ready for one more bite.)
Wild eel grilled over charcoal is...
- very rare.
- It's so delicious.
It's my first time eating this much eel.
It's because it's not greasy. You can't stop eating it.
- It's not greasy at all.
- You keep reaching for more.
I can still remember the feeling of catching those eels.
(Come on, eel. Get in my mouth.)
That's why we worked hard to catch them.
(Everyone is thoroughly enjoying the wild eel feast.)
Gosh, my yakbab.
What's the matter, Jung Ah?
I'll go and take a look.
(She ends up heading over to the yakbab.)
(Has the huge batch of yakbab turned out well?)
(Steam rising)
(It looks well cooked, moist and glistening.)
(Here comes a giant spatula to stir 40 servings all at once.)
(Thick and sticky)
(A drizzle of sesame oil for extra nuttiness)
(Another powerful round of stirring to mix everything evenly)
(This yakbab is for the younger siblings to taste.)
It looks delicious.
I'll check and see if it's cooked.
- All of it is cooked.
- Now...
- Is it cooked?
- It's cooked.
(Hot yakbab goes straight into her mouth.)
Isn't it a little bland?
- It's very bland.
- I know.
I didn't know the exact amount,
so I didn't get the portions right.
It'll taste sweeter once it cools down.
- Really?
- Yes.
(With all her strength)
(The cooked yakbab is transferred into a container.)
(Press it down and shape it even)
This is made with love.
(After sprinkling savory pine nuts)
Once I shape it like this,
- I let it cool...
- Okay.
and slice it later.
Does it taste good? Did it turn out well?
It's very bland.
Then we'll just eat it.
Instead of giving it to them in person,
let's leave it behind with a letter.
(That's original.)
- Let the gesture speak for itself?
- A handwritten letter with love.
- Jung Ah, it tastes good.
- What?
- Does it taste okay?
- It's very good.
(Please turn out delicious)
What time are we getting up tomorrow?
Actually, I have an announcement to make.
It must be a major announcement.
Someone is going to the green tea fields.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Who will it be?
You're in Hadong and Gwangyang right now.
They're Korea's biggest green plum growing regions.
- Green plums?
- I see.
Tomorrow, you're going green plum harvesting.
Unfortunately,
- only three people can go.
- That's so unfortunate.
I really wanted to go.
That's such a shame.
(Gosh, it's such a shame.)
That's a shame. I wanted to go.
Have fun, Yoon Seo.
- Gosh, it's going to make me cry.
- Have fun, Yoon Seo.
Picking green plums is seriously on my bucket list.
(As long as it's not me)
I won't let this slide.
(If I get picked again, I'll be angry at myself.)
Did you see my legs?
I can't even sit down.
I can't sit down or stand properly.
I'm completely worn out.
I've been to every work assignment.
- Let's vote...
- You Seok worked the least.
Jin Hee, what do you think?
What do you want to do?
Tell us what you think.
Jin Hee...
Does he have to list the reasons why he shouldn't go?
Why are you just wiping the table quietly?
- I mean...
- Bring it in.
It's a very simple game.
- Seriously?
- What's that?
It's Americano and...
(Mysterious drinks appear.)
I never imagined that I'd be doing this.
(5 drinks are prepared to select 3 people for green plum picking.)
(2 green plum syrup ades and 3 sand lance sauce drinks)
(Only three people to pick sand lance sauce...)
(go green plum picking.)
(Who will be the lucky ones to meet the green plums of Gwangyang?)
- What is it?
- It's sand lance sauce.
Go ahead and pick first.
They look exactly the same.
This is fun.
- Don't look.
- You have to look.
I've been to every work assignment.
He didn't work even once.
- It's impossible to tell.
- Can we line up...
(They even resort to using their sense of smell.)
(Meanwhile, Sun Young keeps a close eye on the cups.)
Now I know.
(Do you really...)
- You know?
- Yes.
Two of them are clearly Americano.
- There's no Americano.
- There's no Americano, Sun Young.
Two of them are clearly green plum syrup.
Three of them are sand lance sauce.
- You should pick first.
- Okay.
I don't mind being called a braggart,
so I'll tell you the answer.
- Tell us.
- Let's hear it, Sun Young.
- Number 1.
- Is this number 1?
And number four.
This is number one, and it goes in this order.
- In this order?
- Yes.
What's the reason?
- Just because.
- Just because?
It's based on my feelings.
- Your feelings?
- Yes.
- I don't see the color difference.
- You have ten seconds.
(Concentrating)
(Being careful)
(Scanning)
I pick number five.
(Picking number five, which was Sun Young's choice)
- I pick number 2.
- I pick number 4.
Number one.
(Jung Ah who can't decide)
- Yours is number three.
- I'll take what's left.
I have no idea.
(Everyone made their choice.)
I'm really scared.
(Yoon Seo who has been picked for every labor)
(Yum Jung Ah and Roh Yoon Seo, please get up now.)
(You Seok avoided labor for the last 3 days.)
(Determined)
(Sun Young's record: 1 time, onion harvesting)
(Jung Ah's record, 1 time at poultry farm)
(The next workers will be decided purely by luck.)
Let's go.
The color looks strange.
It's red and dark.
(Checking the color one more time)
- Simultaneously...
- Does no one know...
- which one is which?
- I don't know either.
Shall we drink it?
Let's go.
- Okay.
- In the count of three,
- drink it up.
- Without stopping.
Take a big sip?
One.
Two.
Three.
(Drinking)
(Eyes tightly shut)
(Unidentified drinks are gulped down simultaneously.)
(Spitting out sand lance sauce)
(Meanwhile, she moves to minimize the damage.)
(Jung Ah is the first one picked for labor.)
(Is everyone else fine?)
(Of course not)
(Tilting his head)
(Gasping)
(The smell of sand lance sauce hits a beat later.)
(You Seok is picked for labor for the 1st time in 3 days.)
(The intense, umami flavor is hard to shake off.)
(Two workers are chosen.)
I can't drink this.
Is it the three of us?
No, I'm touched.
Who is it?
(There are only 2 cups of green plum syrup.)
Sun Young is holding it in.
Are you holding it in?
(Is either Sun Young or Jin Hee holding in the strong flavor?)
Jin Hee is holding it in.
But it's way too strong.
(Can he really hold it in?)
- Are you crying?
- But it's way too strong.
(However...)
The green plum syrup isn't very good.
Yoon Seo, I asked you to switch with mine.
Try it. It's not good either.
(You Seok grabs Yoon Seo's green plum syrup.)
Yours is sand lance sauce.
Is this sand lance sauce?
Two of them got green plum syrup.
Yours is sand lance sauce.
Is this sand lance sauce?
It tastes similar to green plum syrup.
Can I take a sip of green plum syrup?
Did you think sand lance sauce was green plum syrup?
How could you not tell the difference?
- Is yours green plum?
- Number one was good.
Suddenly, I feel sick.
It hits you late.
She looked so sure of herself.
(She gets picked for labor 3 times in a row.)
I thought number one was...
Sun Young, you said that it was number 2 and 5.
(Sorry about that)
Jung Ah, You Seok, and Yoon Seo will work tomorrow.
Don't you think this is wrong?
(She gets chosen for work 3 times in a row.)
Let's be honest.
I don't think this is right.
Yoon Seo always has work coming her way.
I guess I'm destined to work.
- No, I'm just unlucky.
- You'll work again next time.
Yoon Seo will work until the very end.
You shouldn't say things like that.
She's never skipped work.
Our dear Yoon Seo.
(2 people on house duty, 3 people for green plum harvesting)
I should work since I'm the youngest.
- Jin Hee and I go grocery shopping?
- We'll go grocery shopping.
We need to discuss briefly about serving 40 people tomorrow.
After that, we'll go grocery shopping.
We need to go over this.
When should we go grocery shopping?
You should handle it yourself now.
- Me?
- Yes.
I feel overwhelmed.
She's going to pick green plums,
- so she'll be busy.
- So...
Braised ribs and...
Are we going to make braised ribs?
- Braised pork ribs.
- Braised ribs and pasta.
And seaweed soup.
We're going to make seaweed soup with beef,
so you need to buy some beef too.
Okay, Sun Young?
- Or Sun Young...
- I think we should...
Let's play the game again.
- I want to work with them.
- Why? You...
Grocery shopping without Jung Ah just won't work.
- Because she's our head chef...
- That's not true.
- You just have to buy what we need.
- I can't pick the right things.
I can't pick the right things, Jung Ah.
What's with grocery shopping? It's not so hard.
Are you a good cook?
We're talking about grocery shopping, not cooking.
Sun Young, it's for 40 people.
Are we going to make 40 servings of braised ribs?
- Yes.
But braised ribs... That dish...
Should we use bone-in ribs?
I'll just ask the butcher to prep the ribs.
- Prepping the ribs...
- They prep the ribs for you.
- I mean, they cut the ribs for you.
- Right. They cut the meat.
- Should we just score the meat?
- So...
We have to boil the meat first and then score it...
We have to get pre-cut frozen meat, right?
- You shouldn't get frozen meat.
- We shouldn't?
You should get fresh meat.
- Oh, okay.
- You can just tell the butcher...
- that it's for braised pork ribs.
- Right.
That's at least one piece of meat per person...
No, wait. Each person will have...
- at least two pieces, right?
- Yes.
It has to be at least three pieces per person.
They won't be able to eat that much...
- as they'll have rice and soup too.
- They'll eat at least five pieces.
No, three pieces are the minimum for the elderly.
Prepping the meat will be no joke.
(Buying ribs for 40 people)
(Prepping the meat)
(Cutting and washing)
(It's so important for us to treat the villagers to a proper meal.)
- Jung Ah, I want to go.
- Yes?
- No, that's okay.
- But Jung Ah,
- your back hurts.
- It's been decided. That's okay.
Prepping the ingredients will take a really long time.
- That's true.
- Three hours won't cut it.
- Potatoes and such.
- Yes, chopping them will help.
Exactly. We should chop them so you can use them.
We should wash everything before you come back.
Then we'll have to leave right away,
- but we don't have enough time.
- Right.
Then count me out of picking green plums.
I think I should stay here to shop for the ingredients...
and prep them.
Only then can we save some time for cooking.
It's important to treat the seniors to a proper meal...
as well as to pick green plums.
- I'll go instead of Jung Ah.
- All right.
Right. I'll go.
Let's do our best tomorrow as we always do.
Okay.
(A long, exhausting day is drawing to a close.)
- Good night.
- Sleep well.
(They're going to bed to gear up for tomorrow's work.)
- Good night.
- Sleep well.
Sleep well.
(The night deepens as they wonder what memories tomorrow will bring.)
(As the darkness fades,)
(the sun rises over the mountains.)
(Birds stretch their wings.)
(The sound of clear rushing water wakes the morning silence.)
(Just like that, another day begins in Maegye Village.)
(Stretching his arms)
(It's 6:30am. Jin Hee is the first one up.)
(Grabbing his things)
(He quietly leaves the room without waking You Seok.)
(After showering, Jin Hee sits on the veranda.)
(Then he lies down.)
(He's locked in on stretching while lying down.)
(He keeps on stretching.)
(Flailing his arms and legs around)
(Now that he's all stretched out...)
There's absolutely nothing to do here.
(There's absolutely nothing to do here.)
(So, he heads out for a walk around the village.)
(Impressed)
It's a really nice place to live.
(It's a perfect morning for a walk.)
(Clouds linger around the mountain peaks.)
(Maegye Village looks peaceful with lush green rice paddies and fields.)
(The only sound in this quiet village is the rushing water.)
I really like being in quiet places.
I'm the type...
who gains energy from being alone.
(He's the type who recharges through some alone time.)
Have you done the MBTI test?
I'm an ENTJ.
(Surprisingly, he's an extrovert.)
(The extroverted Jin Hee who claims he likes to be alone...)
I thought my body would ache so much today,
but it doesn't hurt as much as I expected.
I worked hard to finish the work quickly.
I feel like I used every single muscle in my body.
The seniors in this village are incredible.
They do such a great job keeping the fields so neat and organized.
(Clapping)
(He gives off the old-school vibe with his uncle-style clap.)
(This is how Uncle Ji Jin Hee takes a walk in the morning.)
(1. Waking up his system with a healthy clapping routine)
Hello.
You will come over for dinner, right?
I'll see you later.
(2. Talking to seniors)
The red ones...
I think you should eat the darker ones like this.
(Smacking his lips)
(Putting his leg up on the rock)
It's very big.
(If he's curious, he just has to taste it.)
It's sour.
(Chuckling)
I think it's not ripe yet.
This place is really nice.
(3. Taking out his camera when he sees something beautiful)
Oh, this is a wild flower path? I guess that's what it is.
(He spots an information board while walking.)
"As part of the Wild Flower Village Project,"
"we're striving to cover every path in the village with wild flowers..."
No wonder they're well-maintained. The paths looked so beautiful.
"Maegye Village."
"Plum blossom" and "chicken?"
(He makes a dad joke too.)
I wonder if everyone is up now.
(His uncle-style morning walk around the village is almost over.)
(Meanwhile, the girls' room)
My entire body is aching.
I feel like I got beaten up.
Who hit my dear Yoon Seo?
Exactly.
(Screaming)
(The culprit is yesterday's eel work.)
Did you see the people who beat me up?
I saw them.
- I saw three people.
- Three?
Gosh, those brats.
You should've stopped them.
I was getting beaten up too.
(Laughing)
I couldn't stop them.
(She turns out to be another victim.)
- I was getting beaten up too.
- You were getting beaten up too.
(I was getting beaten up too.)
(Jung Ah's body is aching too.)
I feel like I have bruises.
(Victims are popping up left and right.)
- I have the worst muscle pain ever.
- Seriously...
My whole body...
It hurts so much, right?
- It does, indeed.
- The work was very intense.
That's right.
(Dazed)
By the way, Jung Ah...
Can you please get off the mat?
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(Still, we have to do what we have to do.)
- I'll put it over there.
- No.
(You Seok woke up while they were chatting.)
- Good morning.
- You're all up.
- Good morning, everyone.
- Good morning.
Gosh. Why is my whole body aching?
Me too. I feel like I just got beaten up.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Right then, Jin Hee returns from his walk.)
Are you all up now?
- Good morning, Jin Hee.
- Good morning.
- Did you sleep well?
Yes, I did.
I woke up at 6:30am.
At 6:30am?
I took a shower and went for a walk.
- Really?
- Yes.
You went for a walk?
I made it past the village hall on my walk.
Really?
- Is it time to make breakfast?
- Yes.
So the main dish is...
- Gambas?
- Yes.
It's scallop al ajillo.
(Today's breakfast: Scallop gambas)
(Today, they will make gambas with scallop.)
Will it take about 30 minutes to prepare breakfast?
Yes. What are you going to do?
Shall I cut the yakbab and wrap it up?
Will you?
- I have nothing else to do anyway.
- Exactly.
Just show me how to do it.
(Jin Hee will wrap up the yakbab while the others prep breakfast.)
Jung Ah, should I toast some bread?
Yes, we need to toast some bread too.
Then I'll toast bread.
Jung Ah, what vegetables should I wash?
Which vegetables do you need me to wash?
(They say the darkest place is under the candlestick.)
(The vegetables were right under her nose.)
I don't know exactly what dish we're making.
I don't know.
Is it gambas?
(Rinsing cherry tomatoes)
(She puts a cherry tomato in her mouth.)
The cherry tomato is good.
(Destemming the cherry tomatoes thoroughly)
(Putting the cherry tomatoes in her mouth)
(While she's eating the cherry tomatoes...)
Can you help me move the bricks?
- I'll do it. Don't do it.
- It's okay. Let's do it together.
- Do something else.
- Let's do it together.
Do something else. They're heavy.
- Do something else.
- We can get it done quickly.
Find something else to do. Don't do this.
- I'll do it.
- Don't.
- How dare you?
(Making a weird noise)
(Communicating through weird grunts)
- Don't do it.
- No.
(The heartwarming squabble over who gets to do the work)
(Laying down the bricks according to his own plan)
You're doing it weird again.
No, I'm using my artistic sense.
Here you go.
I'll bring you the bricks. You design the layout.
- I should design the layout?
- Yes.
Does this require artistic sense?
Yes, it does. More than anything else.
I feel so pressured.
It's more important than food plating.
(The art major is suddenly in charge of designing the brick stove.)
What should I do? This is the toughest challenge of my life.
(Her pride as an art major is on the line?)
Give it a try. Ignite your passion...
(Brick)
as an artist.
I can bring you all the bricks you need.
(And now she's burning with artistic passion.)
(He provides an endless supply of bricks for the artist.)
(After much deliberation, the brick stove is taking shape.)
Oh, it's big. This is great. It's so pretty.
You did a great job.
(Is this an art major's profound artistic sense?)
(On top of the pretty brick base created by Yoon Seo,)
(he places a burner to complete the brick stove!)
(Jin Hee is getting ready to cut the yakbab.)
(He takes out the yakbab that has perfectly set overnight.)
Just a little bit.
(He coats a spatula with sesame oil to keep the yakbab from sticking.)
(He carefully and meticulously separates the yakbab from the tray.)
(The frown of concentration)
(Flipping over cautiously)
(Perfect)
It's perfect.
- That's amazing.
- Right?
(Now he has to cut it.)
One, two... Six.
(What is he doing instead of cutting the yakbab?)
Three times six equals eighteen. So eighteen pieces.
Four.
(He checks the size in advance to prevent even the slightest error.)
Four pieces. One, two...
That makes 12 pieces. All right.
(A total of 40 servings... If I get 12 pieces per tray...)
Hold on. One, two, three...
(The absolute planner runs a thorough simulation.)
Four times five equals twenty. That means...
Thirty-five...
(Chuckling)
The number of the pieces...
- Are you calculating?
- Yes.
- We shouldn't be short of it.
- He's very meticulous.
I've never counted portions while cooking.
Three times six equals eighteen. So eighteen pieces...
This one is bigger, so...
Even if I get 20 pieces per tray...
(After the seemingly never-ending simulation,)
(he thoroughly coats the knife with sesame oil.)
(Jin Hee keeps the knife from sticking to the yakbab.)
(He's done with the calculation. He's finally cutting the yakbab.)
(He divides it up exactly as planned.)
(Without even the slightest error,)
(he's cutting it smoothly.)
(Cut in a perfectly straight line)
(He's cutting the yakbab with the utmost care.)
(Grunting)
(Thud)
(Groaning)
What's wrong?
(You should've been more careful.)
Seriously, she...
My gosh.
She's done for the day. Seriously.
(Flabbergasted, she collapses onto the floor.)
(Is her soul leaving her body?)
(Dizzy)
(Meanwhile, Jin Hee...)
(He glanced at her and found out she hit her head.)
(Exclaiming)
(Expressing his empathy loud and clear)
Jin Hee, it hurts so much.
(Jin Hee's hands catch Yoon Seo's attention.)
(Whatever is happening around him,)
(he stays focused on cutting the yakbab without faltering.)
Jin Hee...
You wouldn't stop cutting it.
Right. I should do my job no matter what.
- You must be the thinking type.
- Yes, absolutely.
You're absolutely the thinking type.
(Dumbfounded by his icy comfort, Yoon Seo leaves.)
(I have to wrap up the yakbab. I have no choice.)
(Wrapping it up with plastic wrap)
(He's finished packaging one piece of yakbab.)
(He has 47 pieces of yakbab left to wrap up.)
(At the same time, Sun Young)
(Washing garlic)
Let's trim the garlic ends.
- Jung Ah, after doing this, - Yes?
what should I do?
Please slice the garlic.
(Now that it's all cleaned up, it's time to slice it.)
(She slices the garlic, the key ingredient of gambas.)
(Jung Ah...)
(chops the button mushroom.)
(Cutting cherry tomatoes to add a refreshing flavor)
(The base ingredients of gambas are ready.)
I'll help you with that.
I'd be helpful if you can just wrap it up with me.
(While Sun Young joins Jin Hee to package the yakbab...)
(Jung Ah starts making scallop gambas, the main dish.)
I'll put it on low heat.
(You Seok places the oiled wok on the stove.)
(Jung Ah adds the garlic slices nicely cut by Sun Young.)
(Putting them all into the wok)
(The garlic meets olive oil.)
(The aroma of Spain drifts through the air.)
Oh, my. I can smell it.
(Sun Young is the first to catch the aroma of Spain.)
(The Siblings' Spanish Restaurant is now open for business.)
(Adding crushed garlic)
(She adds a whole ladle of it that's not in the Spanish recipe.)
(For Koreans, this much of garlic is just enough.)
(Salt, peperoncino)
It smells amazing.
(She tastes it...)
(and then adds some pepper.)
(Generously adding cherry tomatoes and mushrooms)
(Time for Jung Ah's magic touch)
(Fish sauce)
(Fish sauce adds extra umami and enhances the flavor.)
(As the sauce simmers, it starts giving Spanish vibes.)
(It's time to meet today's star, scallop-flavored crab meat.)
It's crab meat with actual scallops.
- It must be so tasty.
- Yes. It's premium quality.
This one has a buttery flavor. We'll grill it up later.
- We're having a scallop feast.
- I really like scallops.
- You can eat as much as you want.
- It looks so delicious.
(You Seok is in charge of unboxing the scallop-flavored crab meat.)
(It looks so plump that it instantly makes your mouth water.)
I opened all the scallops.
(Today's star is ready to go.)
(Into the perfectly simmered flavorful oil sauce,)
(a generous handful of scallops goes in.)
(It's packed with a punch of spicy umami.)
(While the scallops absorb the gambas sauce...)
I'll grill the scallops now.
(Yoon Seo grills scallop-flavored crab meat with a buttery flavor.)
(As it cooks, the savory butter aroma...)
(drifts through the air.)
(The savory aroma makes her mouth water.)
It looks delicious.
(The butter-grilled scallop-flavored crab meat is cooked to perfection.)
Until it's crispy.
(She toasts baguette slices to pair with the scallop gambas.)
(Meanwhile, how is Team Yakbab Packaging doing?)
(They're almost done packaging 40 servings of yakbab.)
Lift it up, please. There you go.
(They're packaging each piece thoroughly.)
Do you want to try it? Try it.
(Taking a bite)
- It's so good.
- It's good, right?
(Impressed)
Oh, my.
- It's really good.
- Isn't it like a gourmet dish?
- Yes, it is.
- Yes.
(Beautifully packaging the yakbap, as neat and clean as its taste)
Good. It's crispy.
(Now that the baguette slices are ready...)
My, it looks so delicious.
(Serving up a generous portion of the scallop gambas)
- It smells amazing.
- Yes.
With so many scallops, it must be good.
(The scallop gambas with a rich garlic aroma)
(The golden brown, butter-grilled scallops)
(And crunchy kkakdugi)
(A simple yet hearty breakfast is ready.)
- My gosh. Are they all scallops?
- Yes.
- We can eat as many as we want.
- Amazing. We can eat...
- It's a scallop party.
- A scallop party.
You even know how to make this too. You're incredible.
I'm excited to try it.
(It looks delicious.)
How do we eat this, Jung Ah?
Just put some on top of your bread.
- Just put it on the bread?
- Yes.
- Oh, on top of the bread?
You can dip the bread in the oil or top it with scallops.
I'll put one on my bread.
(Crispy)
(Impressed)
- Top it with a scallop, tomato...
- A scallop.
(Building a scallop gambas tower on the bread)
- Like this?
- Put some mushrooms on it too.
(Building a scallop gambas tower on the bread)
(Taking a big bite)
(This is delicious.)
(Sun Young takes a big bite too.)
(Why?)
- It's really plump and tasty.
- Indeed.
It tastes like a real scallop.
(With real scallops inside the crab meat,)
(it's plump and chewy just like real scallops.)
(Jin Hee puts 2 pieces of scallop-flavored crab meat,)
(tomatoes, and mushrooms on top of his bread.)
(Patting them down to keep them from falling off the bread)
(He takes a big bite.)
(Amazed)
After I eat it...
(The chewy texture and refreshing tomato flavor harmonize perfectly.)
The scallop gambas looks so tasty.
(It's good!)
(Crispy)
(Bouncing up and down rhythmically)
- I'll just top it with a scallop.
- It's so good.
- This is so good, Jung Ah.
With a scallop on the bread.
You can eat it as is, and it'd make an amazing salad.
- It'd make a great salad.
- Yes, exactly.
(She takes another bite as it's delicious.)
(She is genuinely loving it.)
(Packed with plenty of garlic, the gambas has a deep, rich umami.)
- It's really good.
- Right?
(Exclaiming)
- Gosh.
- It's good.
(The scallop gambas has captured everyone's taste.)
(Crunchy)
(Impressed)
(A 3-story scallop tower)
(This, right here, is Spain.)
I'm going to cook it myself.
- Seriously.
- Good idea.
I love scallops.
- It's delicious.
- Scallops are always in my freezer.
I love grilled scallops. And this is really good.
(Right up the scallop lover's alley)
- It's good.
- Right? The gambas is amazing.
- Yes, it is.
- It's amazing like this.
- This...
- Has it not been seasoned?
I can't stop myself.
(Loading the bread up until it gets soggy)
(Devouring it in a flash)
This is just too good.
- It's the last one.
- Jung Ah, it's a masterpiece.
(Feeling proud)
(Another bread)
I thought it was scallops.
(Eating)
(And eating again)
(The gambas bewitched Jin Hee.)
I'm eating too much. It's just that good.
I don't usually eat breakfast.
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
(Just when the gambas' greasiness hits,)
(he eats a piece of kkakdugi.)
The kkakdugi is ripe, right?
It's incredible.
(A successful breakfast)
This right here.
I grilled the scallops in butter. Enjoy them as is.
Grilled scallops.
- Scallops.
- Yes.
(Securing a piece quickly)
- It looks rolled up.
- Right?
- It reminds me of flowers.
- Yes.
(They try it together.)
(Amazed)
- A piece of scallop.
- How tender.
It's really savory.
(Packed with rich, buttery flavor)
(Satisfied)
Has it not been seasoned?
- Is it only butter?
- The scallops are coated...
with butter.
(Full of buttery flavor)
(The richness of the butter melts in the mouth.)
Just a bit of pepper.
- It's delicious.
- How is it so...
- Seriously.
- Right?
(He totally agrees.)
(A scallop party the siblings enjoy at full scale)
That was delicious.
Let's go work with a full stomach.
Picking green plums. It's a 50-minute drive.
- We need to fuel up.
- Exactly.
- Fifty minutes?
- Let's go work.
We need to work.
(Let's go pick green plums.)
Let's go.
- I'm ready.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Go.
(Yoon Seo got ready in the meantime.)
Yoon Seo.
(Yes?)
Why do you look so pretty when we're off to work?
(Our dear Yoon Seo)
It's no biggie.
(Why do you look so pretty when we're off to work?)
Then get here already.
I want to take my time.
(I'm going rogue.)
We're off.
- Bye.
- Good luck.
We'll do some grocery shopping...
- and get ready.
- Bye.
Okay.
(The green plum labor team is off to work.)
- Let's go pick green plums - So this is what it's like.
- Let's go pick green plums - It's my first extra labor.
- I'm used to it.
- I didn't gather onions or eggs.
I'm used to it. It's like a daily thing.
So this is how it feels.
Yes, I'm an expert.
(It's Yoon Seo's third extra labor.)
- I love green plums.
- Me too.
- I really love green plums.
- I only bought green plums...
and never picked them.
(A sudden battle of who loves green plums more)
I like the green plum juice.
I even made green plum syrup...
and turned it into green plum syrup soda.
Soda made with green plum syrup is delicious.
(Yoon Seo's love for green plum is endless.)
I've got a ten-year-old green plum syrup at home.
Really?
A ten-year-old green plum syrup tastes totally different.
- I always asked my mom, - The quality is different.
"Mom, why aren't you making green plum syrup this year?"
"Make me green plum syrup soda."
(By the way...)
How do you...
pick the green plums?
- Just pick them.
- They hang like fruits.
- Right?
- Yes.
(You Seok calls someone.)
Is there a way to pick them?
Hello?
Mom.
How do you pick green plums?
Is it some pre-research?
Do you pick them by hand? Do you only pick the fruit?
Not the branch? The top part?
(You Seok's family has a green plum tree at home.)
They have thorns?
But they're not dangerous.
Yes, we're on our way to pick green plums.
Got it.
(The car keeps driving deeper into the dense forest.)
Wait. Those are green plums.
- Really?
- Yes, those are green plums.
(Green plum trees can be spotted on the roadside.)
Green plums.
(Are all of these green plum trees?)
(Arrived at a green plum orchard on the slopes of Mount Baegun)
Let's go.
(I'm here, green plums.)
- Shall we pick some green plums?
- Oh, gosh.
Picking green plums on day three was on my bucket list.
What are those?
- Are they green plums?
But they're not red.
The fruits are green.
This one here is a green plum tree.
- How big.
- Hi.
Hi.
Do we just stand at attention?
Can we relax?
- Tell us.
- Okay.
Gwangyang in South Jeolla Province is...
the largest green plum-growing region in Korea.
We'll be harvesting plums,
a signature summer fruit, here today.
- Okay.
(Gwangyang, Korea's largest plum-growing region)
(Bathed in the pristine waters of the Seomjin River)
With the high...
Mount Baegun behind us,
the environmental conditions here make it an ideal place...
for plums to grow.
(Gwangyang's ample sunshine makes...)
(the flesh plumper and more substantial)
(Growing strong and healthy, filled with plenty of juice)
(The region with exceptionally plump, high-quality plums)
(Today's star, boasting both sweetness and a refreshing tang)
(Gwangyang plums)
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
(A plum blossom headband for a pop of flair)
Thank you. Goodness.
- He's really...
- His skin is flawless.
Well then. What a handsome guy and beautiful ladies.
Shall we head to the plum orchard?
- Yes.
I'll teach you how to pick them.
- Okay.
(Following him into the plum orchard)
- Sir, don't we have to pick...
- The yellow ones...
the plums when they're green?
(As they step into the plum orchard,)
(they spot these plums with a touch of red on top.)
Green plums are picked...
between the end of May and early June.
(Green plums, with their crisp texture,)
(are mainly used to make pickled plums)
(The green plum harvest season is now over.)
(Today, the siblings will be harvesting...)
(slightly blushing red plums.)
Red plums are picked when they turn yellow.
So...
(Red plums are perfect for making plum syrup,)
(bringing out their aroma and flavor.)
(From below, they may look similar to green plums,)
(but red plums are distinguished by the reddish color on top.)
(I'm not a green plum,)
(but I'm still a plum.)
(Green plum, Red plum)
(They're different in both harvest time and variety.)
(How do we pick these plump, luscious plums?)
This is how you pick them.
Pull the plum down,
- and the trunk will break.
- Right.
Twist them when you pick the plums.
- Twist them.
- Got it.
- Right.
- It's easier than you think.
Twist them.
The trunk will break.
(After hearing the full explanation, he suddenly sits down.)
Twist them like so.
(Smelling the plums on the ground)
- Give it a shot.
- Okay.
- Smell it.
- Don't eat them.
- It smells like peaches.
- How fragrant.
The plum smells like peaches.
- Right? It has a strong smell.
- Yes.
What does it taste like raw?
- Is it too bitter?
- Try it.
- It smells peachy.
- The plum smells amazing.
- Try it.
- I want to know how it tastes.
- Do I try it?
- Yes.
Thank you.
(What does the red plum taste like?)
What does it taste like raw?
- Is it too bitter?
- Try it.
- It smells peachy.
- The plum smells amazing.
- Try it.
- I want to know how it tastes.
- Do I try it?
- Yes.
Thank you.
(What does the red plum taste like?)
It tastes different from green plums.
- Unbelievable.
- Let me smell it.
It's literally a peach.
- Right? It smells peachy.
- Yes.
A sour peach.
- Exactly.
- Right?
It's good,
so imagine how delicious they'd be...
- as plum syrup.
- The plum is...
- Oh, my goodness.
- So this is how it tastes raw.
(You Seok also tastes the red plum.)
- It's sour.
- Gosh.
- It tastes peachy.
- Don't step on them.
- Pick them first.
- Shall I try?
- It's sour.
- Pick them first.
(To You Seok, it tastes like a very sour peach.)
Give it a go.
The direction doesn't matter when you twist it, right?
- Grab it and...
- Like this.
- Like so.
- Grab the trunk...
- and twist.
- Got it.
- Do I put it in here?
- Yes.
- In here?
- The bottom.
There's a zipper at the bottom.
Use the zipper to empty the plums into that yellow basket later.
It's true.
(There's a secret to this ordinary-looking apron.)
(Gather the carefully picked plums...)
(in the kangaroo-like pocket in the front)
The plums must roll out...
- when you unzip it.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- That's cute.
He looks like a kangaroo.
(Pouring the plums into the basket fresh off the tree)
- Here I go.
- Try it.
- Okay.
That's it. Just like this.
The plums look nice and ripe.
(As taught, she gently twists them off.)
Really, such cool-looking plums are a first for me.
Goodness. Look at it.
This is a red plum.
I've never seen them before.
Dear viewers, I thought plums were small.
These plums are a first for you too, right?
Plums are good for digestion.
They're also good for digestion.
(Quite short on information)
It must be good for something else too.
The skin is slightly translucent,
so it's like you can see the inside, right?
Look. Have you ever seen such cool-looking plums before?
I hope the camera can catch their texture.
This one's huge.
(The youngest is still mesmerized by the beauty of the red plum.)
I bet it'd be delicious as red plum syrup soda.
The plums look really fresh.
The plums are so pretty. I like them.
- Aren't they pretty?
- Yes.
(The plums are almost too cute not to bite.)
Plums are my all-time favorite.
(One guy is already in love with plums.)
Without plums,
I'm unable to live.
(Without plums, I'm unable to live.)
I drink it every day. I do.
Even my fans know.
I always drink plum beverages...
you could find in supermarkets.
There's a...
plum tree at my parents' house.
When I have...
an upset stomach or eat something greasy,
I have plum syrup at home.
My mom's plum syrup tea.
I don't even know what to say.
With the slightest sign of an upset stomach,
I have the plum syrup.
(His love for plums continues.)
(Already a pocketful to match his love for plums)
It's easy, isn't it, You Seok?
Of course, compared to the eels.
- Totally.
- Guys.
Let's pick a bunch and fast at that.
- Okay.
- We need to go help Jung Ah.
- Good.
- Let's work hard. For real.
- We can do this.
(Searching for red plums)
I won't miss a single plum.
I picked them all.
All done.
(Moving to pick more red plums)
Here they are.
(Picking plums)
(Catching all the plums with hawkish eyes)
(Starting today, I'm the plum catcher.)
(And next to her is...)
(a plum heir focused on the harvest.)
(Picking plums at crazy speed)
How much do we harvest today? All of them?
You're right. What's our goal weight?
- Like this.
- Harvest...
all four trees.
- All four?
- This, that, that, and this.
Four trees.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Do we pick all four trees?
Yes, harvest every plum you see.
(So how big are the four red plum trees?)
(Among the lush green trees)
(Here)
(There)
(And here)
(Plums are hanging from every branch.)
(About 1,000 plums grow on each tree.)
(A challenging target of 4,000 plums to harvest)
I doubt we can harvest all four trees.
We can't.
(Can we pick all the plums?)
We'll be done in a flash. I'll pick two.
Okay. Let's see who can fill up one basket the fastest.
I'm in. Good.
Do you want to make a bet?
- What's the penalty?
- The penalty? He's...
Seriously, you.
- Or the prize.
- What do you want?
- Yoon Seo.
- Yes?
What have you been wanting the most recently?
I want iced coffee right now.
Forget that. Let's raise the stakes.
Raise the stakes?
(What could be a good prize?)
I don't need money.
You know how we make breakfast in the morning?
Allow me to wake up when the breakfast is all set.
(Taking it easy under the covers)
Breakfast is ready.
When I hear "Wake up,"
I'd wake up then and simply eat breakfast.
That's my wish.
(A wish of waking up slowly)
That's my only wish.
You should get Jung Ah's permission for that.
Won't Jung Ah allow it if we say it was the prize...
from a game today?
(Please allow it, Jung Ah.)
Let's do it with the wish on the line.
A bet?
I'm going to go all out, okay?
I'm going all out.
(Plum heir Kang You Seok)
I'm going to work really hard. I'm serious.
You saw that just now, right?
(Falling down)
(Madam Wasp's intimidating spirit makes the plums flee.)
I'm risking my life on it.
Where are they? I can't spot any.
(Plum catcher Roh Yoon Seo)
Is this judged based on...
actual weight or visual weight?
(The one who picks the most wins.)
(Who will win this bet?)
Okay, start.
There must be a method to harvest them fast.
I'll start with the plums hanging lower first.
Branches with many plums are my target.
(Picking up the harvest pace with plums at eye level)
(A determined look)
(I will make my wish come true.)
(Yoon Seo catches the plums Sun Young left behind.)
They're too high up.
Hold on. My height...
(Stretching)
(No matter how much she stretches,)
I can't.
(Yoon Seo can't reach them.)
Look at all of these plums.
(She spotted something.)
(A bonanza of red plums hanging low catches Yoon Seo's eyes.)
Twist them,
so that the stem...
So that the trunk doesn't get hurt.
- Twist them.
- Yoon Seo,
I was saving that good spot to harvest later.
Whatever. I came first.
- It's a bonanza here.
- I came... Stay away!
I don't care.
Look at all of these.
(Sitting down at the bonanza zone)
You...
Why are you here? This is my tree.
Wait, you...
(Picking them quickly)
(Pushing him down)
You...
Hey.
Is that how you're going to play?
(A battle with neither side willing to give an inch)
Oh, seriously.
(These are nobody's. It's 1st come, 1st served.)
(As they compete to pick the plums,)
(the plum-filled branches are picked clean.)
For real?
(Spilling out)
(I picked a bunch, right?)
I want to see how much they've harvested.
I need to do a comparison.
It's to adjust my pace.
Don't tell me they picked a ton.
(Move it.)
- Hold on.
- None have burst.
- What? Why are they so fast?
- You Seok.
Sun Young, You Seok is picking the ones on the ground.
I'm sorry.
- I don't have the time to respond.
- All are yellow.
I can't respond to you.
Yoon Seo is super fast.
How is she that fast?
Yoon Seo's basket gave me a shock.
(The youngsters won't lose.)
(The two spotted the same target.)
No, don't...
What's wrong with you? I'm not stealing yours.
It was my spot, you know?
There’s no yours or mine here.
(He pushes him away.)
What a weirdo.
- Yoon Seo.
- I was already harvesting them.
Stop following me around.
- There aren't any here.
- Stay away.
I'd better pick fast while they're fighting.
Can't you two fight longer? You two.
Guys. Don't you need to chat?
(Groaning)
- Oh, dear.
- Gosh.
(The aftermath of going overboard with passion)
There aren't any trees with red plums.
(Jumping)
(All that's left are red plums up high.)
Nice.
I'm going up.
(Yoon Seo secures an empty basket as well.)
I found a spot with a bunch earlier.
(Searching for the red plums she missed)
There are so many branches.
(It's much easier when standing on top of a basket.)
(The determination not to miss a single red plum)
You have to step back to spot them.
Let me look for some.
- Here they are.
- Oh, dear.
Right here.
Two red plums here.
(She works hard until the very end.)
- It's empty, right?
- Yes.
(Checking again from afar)
From the outside...
We picked every single red plum.
Over there too.
The red plums look very charming.
- Right? The color is...
- They're like gems.
The plums look magical.
It can't be replicated with paint.
Do you know what my life goal is?
What I want to do...
more than a commercial for Chanel is a plum juice commercial.
It's my favorite beverage.
(A plum juice commercial is his life goal.)
(The legendary commercial from back then)
(Cute and tangy, just like a plum)
(I like you.)
(The plum heir's lifelong wish)
Are you ready? I'll do it from up here.
Tell me once you get the angle.
No, I'll...
Please get one full shot...
and one close-up of my hand. We have several cameras.
- Who will take the full shot?
- Me.
Full shot? Okay.
- Nice. It's a good shot.
- Here we go.
- You're the main camera.
Camera roll.
Ready. Action.
(A smooth start, following the game plan)
I like you.
(Dear plum, I like you.)
Do you also like me?
I want to bite you.
(Kissing)
(It's hard to watch her friend on business mode.)
Goodness... He's terribly good.
(Review: He's terribly good.)
I acknowledge him.
(Desperately looking forward to the advertisers' calls)
Okay.
- Nice.
- Lend me the green plums.
(She turns out to be a competitor, not an assistant staff.)
(After borrowing the props, she's ready right away.)
(Action)
I want to bite you.
(Green plums may be pretty, but Yoon Seo is prettier.)
Gwangyang green plums.
(Gwangyang green plums are as refreshing as me.)
(The video won't end.)
It really looks like a commercial.
Did mine look like a fake one, then?
- I'm getting more shameless here.
- You only favor the youngest.
(My green plums commercial.)
Are you done picking?
- Yes.
- Let's go pick Japanese apricots.
- What?
- What apricots?
Japanese apricots.
- There's more?
- Yes.
(Meanwhile, at home)
(Before going to grocery shopping, Jung Ah...)
Pork ribs.
How much pork ribs should I buy?
How much do I need to buy to cook for 40 people?
(She is lost in thought to cook such a big portion.)
Add some shishito peppers.
(Let's go buy groceries before it's too late.)
- Let's go.
- Pork ribs, soju,
shiitake mushrooms, carrots,
radish, green onions, shishito peppers, coke.
- We should buy two watermelons.
- Right.
- Let's finish it in 20 minutes.
- Okay.
(They even decide the duration for grocery shopping.)
- It's 11:28am. Then...
- Right.
when we come back,
it'll be 1pm. We'll be back around the same time...
- as the rest.
- Earliest 1pm.
(How will the planning duo make use of the time?)
It's 1pm, and we need to go...
- and prepare food by 5pm.
- Right.
(She writes down the timeline.)
We need to prepare the meat beforehand, right? Boil them first.
Just add Coke to hot water...
and broil it for 3 to 5 minutes.
Then it's like this.
As soon as we arrive,
- we'll boil water in a big pot...
- Prepare the water first?
- and boil it.
- Let's boil it a bit first.
As the water boils, we can do other things.
Yes.
Do you add the water after the water boils,
or pour cold water onto the meat and boil them together?
- Into boiling water...
- You add the meat.
- Yes. Broil it for 3 to 5 minutes.
- Then...
- Okay.
- We'll take the meat out...
and wash it in cold water.
If you add meat to hot water,
- the water temperature drops.
- Yes.
Is it three minutes from there,
or three minutes after the water starts boiling again?
(This question is a first.)
- Let's just do roughly 5 minutes.
- Okay, 5 minutes.
I'm an extrovert.
(An extrovert)
- You're the planning type.
- The planning type.
(Embarrassed)
If I have enough time,
I want to make zucchini jeon too.
- Shred zucchini and...
- It's delicious.
Zucchini jeon is nice and sweet.
It's delicious. Just add Cheongyang chili pepper.
It's not difficult, right?
- Just shred it and...
- But shredding...
- You can use the mandoline too.
- Exactly.
Zucchini. I'm sure they have lots of pan-frying powder.
Go. I'll follow you.
(How will the planning duo grocery shop?)
- Throw things inside.
- Okay.
Let me check how much pork ribs they have.
Ribs first.
- Hello.
- I need to cook pork ribs today.
- Pork ribs.
Give me 10kg of pork ribs.
Nice.
We'll go down one aisle each.
- The sauce.
Actually, this isn't...
(Zucchini)
(A lot)
We need ten at least.
Green onions, shishito peppers, and shiitake mushrooms.
(Shishito peppers)
(Mushrooms)
(Tomatoes)
Nice.
Sure.
- We're good. This much will do.
- Okay.
(The grocery shopping is over in 10 minutes.)
(I'm excited.)
(With the planning duo, grocery shopping in bulk is easy.)
The whole place is green.
These are Japanese apricots.
- They're red?
- These?
Gosh, they're so pretty.
(Japanese apricots won You Seok's heart at once.)
(They're redder than red plums.)
(Japanese apricots: Both the skin and the flesh are red.)
(They stay red when made into juice or wine.)
(Out of the three types of plums, they're harvested the latest.)
(Let's pick Japanese apricots, which have different charms.)
- First time seeing them?
- Yes.
Hold the branch like this.
(They're plucked the same way as red plums.)
(The experienced worker's body moves first.)
Let's go.
(Picking right away)
Let's go!
- Japanese plum... Japanese apricot?
- Japanese apricot.
- I've never heard of it before.
- Goodness.
(Even You Seok, who's familiar with a lot of plums, hasn't heard of it.)
It has a cute size.
It's like a mini apple.
(It's cute like a mini apple.)
Pick.
(Picking)
(The apricot picker has learned to pick with both hands.)
(Everyone is picking...)
(Japanese apricots.)
This is fun.
It has such a pretty color.
(Entranced by picking Japanese apricots)
- This feels really good.
- I know, right?
(The siblings pick the whole trees bare.)
(They don't miss a single apricot on the ground.)
Dear viewers, if you miss now, you can't see Japanese apricots.
Now's the right time.
(Introducing it secretly to her beloved viewers)
We're done picking.
We've finished? Okay.
We're done.
(They empty their kangaroo aprons one last time.)
(Falling)
(Emptying their pockets and not leaving anything inside)
- The bet still stands, right?
- It does.
(Time to check the weight and decide a winner)
(Who picked the most red plums and Japanese apricots?)
(Measuring Sun Young's basket first)
(Sun Young's red plums: 12.5kg)
(Sun Young's Japanese apricots)
(9.5kg, Total: 22kg)
It's 22kg.
(What about Yoon Seo, the plum catcher?)
It's 15kg.
- Gosh, Yoon Seok.
- How much?
(Japanese apricots)
- It's 10kg.
- Total 25kg.
(Total: 25kg)
(In last place, 22kg, Currently in 1st place, 25kg)
(Lastly, You Seok's full basket)
(Heavy)
That looks like 30kg.
(Will he place 1st like the gamer he is?)
(Red plums alone are 24kg.)
- We can't beat him.
- This alone beats you.
I told you we couldn't.
(The Japanese apricots You Seok picked)
It's 7kg.
Thank you. Good job.
(You Seok wins with a total of 31kg.)
- He's insane.
- Thank you. Good job.
Good job.
- Thanks for your hard work.
- Thank you.
- Was it doable?
- Yes.
(Getting the products is as exciting as picking.)
- Green plum syrup and pickled plum.
- Pickled plum.
- My gosh.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Good job.
- Thank you so much, sir.
- Thank you for this.
- Amazing.
This is so precious. Thank you so much.
Goodness. It's precious pickled plum.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for your hard work.
(The plums picked like this...)
We separate them using the grader.
(They're sorted according to the size.)
They're sorted according to the size.
And we ship them.
(They were delivered nationwide.)
- Good job.
The hard part starts now.
(It's time to prepare the ingredients for Eat Together.)
(The planning duo has everything planned.)
- Start the fire for the pork.
- I got you.
- We'll boil water in a big pot...
- Prepare the water first?
- and boil it.
- Let's boil it a bit first.
(Setting the burner to boil the water)
Just nice.
(Preparing the water to boil pork ribs)
(Complete)
(Plan 2. Soak out the blood of pork ribs)
That's it. Hey.
I'm fine. I can do this much.
(Soak out the blood in cold water.)
(The blood soaks out with impurities.)
(Soak out the blood of pork ribs)
(Complete)
(The water is starting to boil.)
Are you adding Coke now?
I brought the Coke. Please move that to here.
The Coke...
- The Coke...
- I need to add the Coke.
Will you add it and boil them, or boil them and add it?
I'm the planning type.
(Even Jung Ah is overwhelmed by Jin Hee's detailed questions.)
(Chef Yum's tip: Add Coke when boiling pork ribs...)
(to tenderize the meat and add umami.)
(It's time to add pork ribs.)
- Add as much as you can.
- Okay.
(Adding pork ribs into the coke water)
Let's broil it for 5 minutes. I'll set 5 minutes.
(A timer is a must for the planners.)
I don't think the others will be here by the time we're done.
- Then...
- What other things are there to do?
- wash the vegetables.
- Yes.
- I'll score the meat.
You do this.
Okay.
- Time's up, right?
- Yes.
Okay.
This is enough.
(The first round of boiling is complete.)
It looks good.
That's it.
(It's time to wash them.)
(Rinsing with cold water)
All of these are done to get rid of...
the gamey taste of meat.
(Wash boiled meat with cold water to get rid of the gamey taste.)
Don't miss a single piece.
(Jin Hee gets ready to shred zucchini.)
Can I ask...
how long...
- the zucchini should be?
- That's not it.
If you cut it like this, it becomes long,
and if I do this, it becomes short.
(His detailed questions are back.)
- Like this...
- You can't do that. Cut it long.
No, slant it.
- Long slices like this?
- Your hand. Yes.
- Yes. Watch out for your hand.
- Long?
Yes.
Like ramyeon or noodles?
Then?
- No.
- Then?
Not as long as ramyeon.
- About 45 degrees?
- Yes. Try it.
Push it upward.
(Reaching a compromise)
(While Jin Hee shreds the zucchini,)
(the pork ribs washed in cold water...)
(are ready to be scored now.)
I'm scoring the meat so the soup will seep in well.
(Slicing each and every meat with care)
You must really like cooking.
- You're humming.
- I really like it.
When we bought a lot of ingredients...
(She felt the excitement since grocery shopping.)
- I really felt good.
- Since we bought groceries?
- Yes.
- You felt happy at the thought...
of cooking?
I cooked various food on this show.
- You're right.
- And the members...
always enjoy my food.
- It makes me want to do better.
- I see.
(Shredded zucchini has become a pile.)
I'll put this in the master bedroom.
(She's done preparing the pork too.)
- I'll just chop them.
- Okay.
Give me those.
We're back.
- Thanks for your hard work.
- Good job.
Goodness.
- Take a rest.
- This is killing me.
You worked so hard.
No, I think you had it worse.
Jung Ah.
- Good job.
- We're back.
We'll take over now.
- No, take a rest.
Eat something.
You look so exhausted.
- It's so good.
- Right?
(Taking a big bite)
(The planning duo is preparing the ingredients.)
(Shishito peppers, red peppers, shiitake mushrooms, carrots)
(Preparing quickly)
(The vegetables for braised pork ribs are ready.)
What can we do to help?
Let's head over now.
- Shall we?
- Let's continue there.
Sounds good.
(She ties the bandana resolutely.)
(He packs the ingredients.)
I can put this here.
I'm so happy.
Before doing something,
shout "I'm excited" loudly.
It activates your brain and improves productivity.
- One, two, three.
- I'm excited!
Yes!
(The siblings cooking crew heads off excitedly.)
Yes.
I love the song choice too.
- Thank you.
- Get out.
- Are we going to do this?
- Good.
(They take out the ingredients and other stuff they prepared.)
Unfold it.
Just take the light ones first.
Can you carry it?
(They take out the ingredients and other stuff they prepared.)
(Meanwhile, impatient Captain Yum...)
(heads straight to Eat Together.)
We're late.
(She rushes into the building.)
(Glancing)
(The space for around 40 people to eat...)
(and a kitchen...)
(as big as any other restaurant)
(She's getting very impatient.)
We don't have much time. Let's hurry.
(Current time: 3pm)
(Remaining time: 2 hours 30 minutes, including the setting time)
(Today's menu: Plain rice, wild rock seaweed soup with beef,)
(braised pork ribs, tomato pasta, zucchini jeon)
We need to soak the seaweed, right?
Yes, soak the seaweed.
(Checking the pots for cooking in big bulk)
I'll use that for seaweed soup,
and this for braised pork ribs.
(It's the perfect size for braised pork ribs.)
(They start cooking in earnest.)
(The planner Jin Hee moves according to the plan.)
I need to wash, mash, and mince tomatoes, right?
(Planner Jin Hee's plan: 1. Wash, mash, and mince tomatoes)
Next, mince onions.
Before that, pour the meat into this.
Pour the meat.
(Pork ribs boiled once)
Wait.
(He's flustered by the unexpected weight of pork ribs.)
(Struggling)
(Even Jin Hee is barely able to carry the ribs for 40 people.)
(Frowning)
(Since it's heavy, let's move it to the pot quickly.)
Done.
(The ribs fill up the pot.)
You Seok, here.
Onto the stove.
(The portion is so big that two men need to pour and carry them.)
(Thud)
(Even the sound is heavy.)
(The large volume of ribs...)
(are drenched in soju again.)
This needs to be grilled for a long time.
(While it's left to remove the gamey taste...)
(Jin Hee takes the vegetables to be prepared.)
Jin Hee, I was going to wash them.
- Were you?
- Yes.
Thank you.
(As expected, Yoon Seo knows what to do without being told.)
(She washes the tomatoes thoroughly.)
(Delivering quickly)
(Jin Hee gets ready to cut them right away.)
(He crushes the tomatoes mercilessly.)
(With his vein-popping forearm,)
(he smashes the tomatoes mercilessly.)
(He's a human blender.)
(What used to be tomatoes)
(After crushing them to his satisfaction,)
(as befitting of a craftsperson, he switches to a mincing knife.)
(This time, he minces them mercilessly.)
(While he minces the tomatoes...)
(You Seok is in charge of cooking rice.)
(He starts washing the rice.)
(But how much rice does he need to pour?)
Do I fill up half the pot?
(Thinking)
How big is the pot? For 20 people?
(It's first time for Captain Yum to cook rice for 40 people as well.)
I think this is too little. Fill up half at least.
(As confirmed by Captain Yum, he fills up half the pot.)
(He starts washing the rice.)
(He needs to wash 3 to 4 times to wash it properly.)
(But the amount of rice he needs to wash...)
(is for 40 people.)
(It's incomparable to the rice...)
(he prepared for 4 people.)
(He washes...)
(and washes.)
(But there's no end to it.)
We're really short of time, aren't we?
It feels like we're on a cooking show.
You're right.
(The start to an unending rice-washing)
(Another large volume, zucchini jeon)
Jung Ah, did you say to salt this?
Don't I just need to add the pan-frying powder?
No.
- Salt it so it produces water.
- I need to salt it?
We need to use the water.
(It'll be kneaded with the water produced from being salted.)
A pinch?
(For 40 servings of zucchini jeon...)
Twenty pinches. Two...
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight...
Flip it around and add ten more pinches.
(For the salt to soak in thoroughly,)
(mix the zucchini well.)
(10 more pinches of salt)
(Zucchini has become moist now.)
And...
I'll mix it now.
Okay.
(Add sliced peppers.)
(Pour pan-frying powder on top of it.)
(She starts to mix them!)
(Adding water and pan-frying powder bit by bit)
(It's important to make sure it doesn't become clumpy!)
(Adding)
(Adding again)
(Mixing until her arm hurts)
(Before you know it,)
(she's finished a whole pack of pan-frying powder.)
(The portion is so big that it needs a whole pack.)
(Starch on top of it)
(Never ending rice-washing and mixing)
(While the two are stuck in the infinite loop...)
(Jung Ah is in front of the countertop.)
(She takes out a piece of paper?)
(To Captain Yum, failure is not acceptable!)
(Since she's cooking braised pork ribs in bulk...)
(for the first time,)
(she's calculated the recipe thoroughly in advance.)
(She checks the recipe...)
(and measures accurately using a measuring cup.)
(As per her calculations)
(2 cups of 165ml)
(4 cups of 165ml)
(5 cups of 165ml)
(2 and a half cups of sugar)
(Next...)
(Is that mustard paste?)
When you add mustard paste to the soy sauce,
- the unpleasant odor is gone.
- Does it taste clean?
Yes. The meat doesn't smell bad, and it gets more flavorful.
It works perfectly when you make bulgogi too.
(It's good when you make bulgogi too.)
(2 cups of minced garlic)
(Last, she adds minced ginger.)
(After a good mix, the sauce for braised ribs is ready.)
(She adds it straight to the short ribs.)
(She pours water into the remaining sauce...)
(and adjust the saltiness of the sauce.)
(Boil it for a while until the ribs absorb the sauce.)
(In the meantime, You Seok escaped the rice-rinsing abyss.)
(However,)
(he doesn't know much water he should put in to cook rice.)
Jung Ah, is this enough water?
Jung Ah, you should hold it.
(When he doesn't know something, he seeks Jung Ah.)
Even if I look at it...
- How much water do we need?
- I don't know it either.
- For this amount...
- How many cups of rice is this?
(Except for the pasta,)
(they're serving Korean dishes, so rice is important.)
I can't tell how much water I should put in.
Exactly.
I think we might need to add more water.
- Do you want it firm or soft?
- What?
Firm rice or soft rice?
Whatever the older people like.
It shouldn't be too firm.
- It should be a bit soft, right?
- Yes.
Shouldn't the water cover the back of your hand?
- No?
- We need to add more water...
- because it's lots of rice.
- Exactly.
We need to add more water.
(They solved the problem quickly thanks to Jin Hee's call.)
(They add more water until it covers the back of his hand.)
(Rice for 40 people is coming through.)
- Gosh.
- Is it too much?
Amazing.
(Starting the rice cooker!)
The rice is going to be okay, right?
(The rice will turn out okay, won't it?)
(Here's another person who fell into the abyss.)
(Escaping the abyss)
(She finally completes the batter for 40 people.)
(Now, it's time to fry zucchini jeon.)
(She'll make palm-sized pieces for them to eat comfortably.)
(Okay. She got it.)
(She drizzles oil into the electric griddle.)
(She puts a spoonful of the batter on the griddle.)
(Tapping)
(Spread it thinly with a gentle touch.)
(Sizzling)
(Am I good or what?)
(The heat is strongest in the center.)
(She switches places, so the pieces are cooked evenly.)
(When one side gets golden,)
(she flips the piece so it won't burn.)
(The hands of a seasoned jeon-maker)
(For some reason,)
(Sun Young looks like a jeon-making pro.)
Can you feel it?
Can you tell that I've made many jeon before?
My body doesn't shake, does it?
Inexperienced people can't keep it steady.
They go like this, but that isn't me.
Though it's been about ten years since I made one,
I'm very relaxed.
(The master of jeon is filled with confidence.)
This one is an art.
Look at this, Jin Hee.
Isn't it awesome?
(Dropping his jaw indifferently)
I like to cook them until golden like this one.
Something like this. What do you say?
- That's great.
- The less-cooked ones aren't tasty.
They aren't tasty.
It should be slightly crispy on the outside...
- and soft on the inside.
- Yes. Slightly. I agree.
- She knows what's up.
- This one looks amazing.
But I need to...
I need to try it to decide whether I should keep going...
or make changes by adding something.
(The younger ones jump at the chance to try it.)
- They look nice and pretty.
- Jin Hee.
Can someone come and try it quickly?
If it tastes good,
- I'll use the batter as is.
- The taste testers are here.
- Can I try it?
- Of course.
- We need to taste it.
- We're the tasters. Tear it.
I can't try it because I'm full.
It's hot.
It's hot. Darn it.
(Sacrificing their bare hands because they want it so bad)
- It's hot.
- Hold on.
I can't do this.
(Grabbing it gently to avoid the heat and taking a bite)
Are there chopsticks somewhere?
(This time, her mouth burns.)
This isn't the final result.
I'm going to eat it anyway even though it's hot.
Try it, and tell me how it tastes.
Cool it down before you eat.
(Putting it straight into her mouth...)
(and letting it cool down a bit)
I can't try it. I ate too much.
Tell me already.
(How does the master's zucchini jeon taste?)
(Jung Ah, the head chef, tries a bite too.)
I think it's good.
- Really?
- I think it's good too.
(It tastes good.)
It's good.
- It's delicious, isn't it?
- It's delicious.
It's tasty.
Then I'll go on with this one.
- Okay.
- Yes. Sounds good.
Okay. That's how it's going to taste.
(Let's make a massive batch of zucchini jeon with this batter.)
(Because she has to make 40 servings,)
(she fills up the griddle with many pieces.)
(Cooking 9 pieces at once)
(Hard at work)
(Current time: 3:40pm)
(1 hour and 50 minutes left, including setup time.)
(Progress: Rice 80, Braised ribs 40, jeon 15, pasta 5)
(Wild rock seaweed soup with beef: 0 percent)
(The pot for the seaweed soup is still empty.)
(Someone should start making it.)
(At that moment, Yoon Seo grabs a pan...)
(and stands next to the stove.)
I'll try making the seaweed soup.
- I've made it before.
- Okay. Go for it.
I've made seaweed soup a few times.
Right. You make it on birthdays.
That's right.
(She pats the beef dry with a paper towel,)
(drizzles sesame oil into the pan,)
(then adds the beef.)
(She adds the cooking wine to remove unpleasant odors.)
(She wasn't kidding when she said she made it before.)
(She stir-fries the meat skillfully.)
As for the seaweed...
Wild rock seaweed? You need to cut it.
- Where is it?
- I need to stir-fry it with this.
- Did you soak it in water?
- Can you...
No, I didn't soak it in water.
No?
(The wild rock seaweed is neglected in the corner of the kitchen.)
You need to soak it in water and chop it.
This isn't chopped seaweed.
I need to cook the beef later, then.
(She forgot to soak the seaweed in water and got ahead.)
(She quickly fills a big bucket with water.)
I'll soak it in water.
Okay.
(She soaks the wild rock seaweed in water in a hurry.)
(She tears it into pieces...)
(to speed up the soaking process.)
(You Seok joins the soaking task.)
Are you going to use all of this?
It's the one we dried ourselves.
Exactly. It's the one we made.
It's from back then.
(Tasty wild rock seaweed...)
(they harvested in Gyeonnaeryang, Geoje)
(They've prepared it just for the elderly here.)
(When the seaweed fully absorbs the water...)
It doesn't need to be cut finely.
- Okay.
I'm just cutting the long pieces.
- I'm cutting the stems.
- Yes.
(Cut it again into bite-sized pieces.)
(In the meantime,)
(beef for the soup base is cooked and ready.)
(Now, it's really the time to cook seaweed soup.)
(Adding a generous amount of the wild rock seaweed)
It tastes better with lots of seaweed...
- and with less broth.
- Okay.
(Adding a generous amount of the wild rock seaweed)
- I'm going to add a bit of garlic.
- Okay.
Am I wrong?
How much minced garlic should I add?
- Like this much?
- But Jung Ah...
Yes. You can add more.
(When Jung Ah seasons it with the soy sauce for soup...)
Yes. We need to add more water.
Just enough to cover the ingredients.
- Like this much?
- Yes.
- Should I add more minced garlic?
(After adding a little more minced garlic,)
Let's boil it for now.
Boil it.
(they'll bring it to a boil so that the soup absorbs...)
(the rich flavors of the wild rock seaweed.)
(Jin Hee has finished prepping the tomatoes.)
- What do I have to do now?
- What?
What do you want me to do?
- Something else.
- I have a job for you.
- Jin Hee.
- Yes?
- A spoon.
- Yes. Please get another spoon.
Okay.
(Sun Young could only make this much by herself.)
(If 1 person gets 2 pieces of jeon,)
(they need to make 80 pieces of jeon in total.)
(It's still far from enough.)
If you cook it over there, I'll cook it over here.
Okay.
- Please make two rows.
- Okay.
- You want it to be that big.
- Yes.
(Jin Hee, a hardcore planner, measures the batter with a ladle...)
(to get the exact same amount.)
It can be a bit thinner.
(Pausing)
(In that case, he puts less on the pan.)
(Tapping)
Goodness. You made thin ones because I asked for them.
You're amazing.
Its thickness has changed noticeably.
(The master of jeon is no match for him.)
(He's too good.)
Do you cook at home?
- Never.
- Me neither.
My wife won't allow me in the kitchen.
- Then...
- She's like, "This is my turf."
- "Don't come in."
- Why are you so good at chopping?
- I'm good with my hands.
- Why? Why is it?
Doing something with my hands is my specialty.
That's right. You're a craftsman.
Yes. So, when I make things with my hands,
- I'm good at it.
- I forgot about it.
Yes. You're a craft artist.
(On top of having pretty shapes,)
It cooks faster since it's thin.
(the zucchini jeon cooks faster...)
(because Jin Hee made it thin.)
(When Jin Hee makes a thin piece on the pan,)
(Sun Young flips it...)
(as soon as it's cooked.)
(They've made this many already.)
- Oil doesn't scare me.
- Okay.
You're not afraid of making something.
- I'm not afraid at all.
- No.
(With their increased synergy,)
(the zucchini jeon starts to pile up quickly.)
(Are the braised ribs cooking well?)
(Opening the lid)
(As the ribs cook, lots of impurities have come out.)
(To remove bad odor and make it taste clean,)
(she removes the oil and impurities completely.)
(Then she adds the vegetables.)
(She adds potatoes and carrots first as they need to be cooked longer.)
(Healthy shiitake mushrooms...)
(and various vegetables are added.)
(Adding a drizzle of starch syrup)
(After mixing them together to cook thoroughly,)
(it looks tasty already.)
Jung Ah, now...
(She lets it cook a little more over low heat.)
(How is the seaweed soup looking?)
- See if you need to add more water.
- Okay.
(Surprised)
Seriously. I've never cooked this much before.
(The wild rock seaweed soup looks rich and flavorful.)
We'll add water up to here, and let it simmer.
(Yoon Seo will finish cooking the wild rock seaweed soup.)
(Adding 2L of water as it's for 40 people)
I'll add a dash of anchovy sauce, Jung Ah.
(Increasing its umami with anchovy sauce)
(And how will it taste?)
(Satisfied)
Let me try it too.
- Gosh.
- It needs to simmer for a while.
Gosh. Wild rock seaweed is different, indeed.
(The wild rock seaweed makes it richer and flavorful.)
It looks good.
(Let's boil it for a while for a richer flavor.)
(Including the seaweed soup, the dishes are 90 percent ready.)
(Current time, 4:40pm)
(Time left: 50 minutes)
(They have extra time because they hurried.)
(Jung Ah looks around the kitchen while catching her breath.)
(They cooked a massive amount for the first time...)
(without any problems.)
(The siblings' cooking crew is running smoothly.)
Good job.
(Now all that's left to make is the tomato pasta.)
I'll make the sauce over here.
(Prepping the sauce right away for the final push)
(How will Chef Yum make the pasta sauce for the elderly?)
(Adding lots of minced garlic to the heated olive oil)
Gosh. Pasta.
(For older guests not familiar with tomato pasta...)
It looks good already.
- You only cooked garlic, - Yes.
- but it smells good already.
- Cooked garlic is always tasty.
(Adding a touch of Italian flavor with peperoncino)
(And...)
(here comes what Jin Hee chopped with care.)
(She sautes tomatoes and onions.)
(Adding the tomato paste)
Let's simmer it after adding the sauce
(Adding black pepper)
(Let it simmer for a while,)
It smells so good.
(and the sauce is ready.)
(Smiling)
- It's good.
- Is it?
Do you want to try it?
(Satisfied)
- It's good, isn't it?
- It's delicious.
Now, let's finish it up after cooking the noodles.
We're going to cook the noodles last.
(The dishes are almost done.)
- Join us, Yoon Seo.
- Me?
"Hello, we're Fresh off the Sea's..."
"Yum Jung Ah, Kim Sun Young, and Roh Yoon Seo."
(The three sisters will make an announcement...)
(over the village PA system.)
"We've prepared a meal for you with love and care."
"Please come by 5:30pm..."
(Sneaking a peek)
to EAT-together MAEGYE.
We'd greatly appreciate it.
Please come to EAT-together MAEGYE.
- That's done.
- Wait. Look.
They're all gathered together already.
(After wrapping up the day's work early,)
- Some came out early.
- Yes.
(the villagers are gathered for a workout.)
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
Gosh. That's right.
- Kwang.
- That's right.
How have you been, Kwang?
- Look at him greeting us.
- That's right, Kwang.
Kwang.
You're so pretty.
You're adorable.
Gosh. You're so pretty and cute.
Goodness. Good afternoon.
(The older sisters in the meantime...)
- When you make the announcement, - Hello.
push this button, and turn this on.
(The announcement begins after pushing the bell button.)
They'll focus on the announcement.
Please turn it on for us, then we'll make the announcement.
(The village PA mic is on.)
Good afternoon.
We're Fresh off the Sea's Yum Jung Ah...
Good afternoon,
everyone in the village.
I'm Kim Sun Young.
- Next to me is...
- I'm Roh Yoon Seo.
(The three sisters' first village PA announcement)
Yes. Today,
we've prepared a meal for you with care.
We'd much appreciate it...
if you come to EAT-together MAEGYE...
by 5:30pm.
Come for dinner by 5:30pm.
It's at 5:30pm.
Please come...
and enjoy the dinner.
- Okay.
- Please come.
Please come. We've prepared a delicious dinner.
Bye.
(Feeling embarrassed after making the announcement)
(Please come, everyone, and enjoy a warm meal.)
How much time do we have?
(Current time: 5pm, 30 minutes before serving)
Okay. You're doing great.
- Gosh. They made so many.
- I know.
(How does well-simmered wild rock seaweed soup taste?)
(Satisfied)
It's good.
(She keeps simmering it so it doesn't cool down.)
(The wild rock seaweed soup with beef is 95 percent done.)
It smells like tasty braised ribs.
(Tasting the meat with the younger siblings)
- Jung Ah, it's so good.
- Yes? Does it taste good?
- Yes, it tastes good.
- It's well-seasoned, right?
(It tastes good.)
(Jin Hee tries a piece of meat too.)
Gosh. It's perfect.
- Does it taste okay?
- Yes.
Simmer it over low heat. Over very low heat.
(The braised pork ribs are 95 percent done.)
What do we have to do now?
- What?
- Are we done after cooking pasta?
- We have to make pasta, right?
- Yes.
- What do we do for pasta?
- Should we cook the noodles?
Let's bring water to a boil and make pasta.
(Getting ready to cook pasta noodles)
(The tomato pasta is 50 percent done.)
We'll add the noodles later.
- Did we fluff the rice?
- Please check the rice.
- Let's fluff the rice.
- Rice...
- Is the rice cooked?
- Check the rice.
- It's on Keep Warm now.
- Yes.
We need to open it to see...
- What if it isn't cooked?
- No way.
It must be cooked well.
I have to remake it right away if it isn't cooked well.
(Nervous)
If the rice isn't cooked well, we're in trouble.
- The rice is... Hold on.
- It's okay, isn't it?
I'll take some out and fluff the rest.
What should I do now?
I want you to oversee everything...
related to setting up the table while we finish up cooking.
- We'll serve the food, right?
- Yes.
Get kkakdugi and others ready.
Gosh. Kkakdugi looks delicious.
(Portioning it out for easy serving)
(She takes as much as she cares for the villagers.)
I think that's too much.
You can grab more when you run out of it.
(She portions out just the right amount.)
- Should I add a final spoonful?
- Yes.
- I'll take yakbab out now, Jung Ah.
- Okay.
Right, Jung Ah?
- I'll make a pretty circle.
- Okay.
There are a lot, so you can stack them up.
(Stacking them up)
Yes. When you make a big pile, it looks more delicious.
(Scraping the batter)
- Amazing work, Jin Hee.
- Good job.
(The long process of frying jeon finally comes to an end.)
Gosh. Ms. Roh has set up jeon nicely.
(Braised ribs, pasta, seaweed soup)
(They'll set up the rest later.)
- I'll open the packets, Chef.
- Okay.
(I'll open the pasta noodle packets, Chef.)
Are you playing a restaurant game right now?
(Laughing)
This isn't a game.
- We're doing it for real.
- Is it?
We have a reservation for a group of 40 at 5:30pm, Chef.
- Please get into it, Chef.
- Should I?
(Awakened Chef Yum adds the noodles to the water.)
Are we making the pasta finally?
We're cooking the pasta noodles now.
(3 packets)
(Adding a massive amount...)
Let's use all of them.
(of the pasta noodles)
(Salt)
Let's cook the noodles for ten minutes.
- We have time, right?
- Yes.
We have plenty of time. We're waiting to be on time.
(Since they have time, they clean up in advance.)
Hey, you're here. Did you smell the food?
(The first guest of the EAT-together MAEGYE)
(Sun Young is enjoying the time with the puppies.)
The two came running at the smell of the food...
like students rushing to school.
(Something smells good here.)
(Where? I'm coming too.)
(Some customers are already here before the opening.)
(Meanwhile, Jung Ah checks the pasta noodles.)
This is driving me crazy.
It's hard to cook them. They soak up all the water.
- Is it over high heat?
- Yes. I cranked up the heat.
(Serious)
- We have to boil it for a while.
- They are coming now.
- What?
- They're starting to gather.
(Current time: 5:15pm)
(It's already 15 minutes before serving.)
(I'm hungry.)
(The villagers leave their home for the meal.)
(The Siblings', but the cooking crew is...)
It's not easy to cook the noodles.
(The pasta is still undercooked.)
(Braised ribs and seaweed soup must be set up too.)
(Chef Yum is deep in thought.)
You Seok, we need to add more hot water.
It absorbed a lot of water.
Let's add a bit more.
(They decide to tackle the most urgent pasta first.)
(Cooking fast by adding hot water)
Could you move that?
- This...
- Should I move this?
- Hey.
- Gosh, where should I put it?
- Put it there.
- Okay.
Put it down.
(Wild rock seaweed soup with beef is also ready to be served.)
I'll finish making the braised ribs.
(Adding loads of sesame oil and sesame seeds)
It looks delicious.
It's seasoned perfectly.
(The braised ribs are completely ready.)
Could you put the braised ribs on a plate?
(Portioning braised ribs begins.)
What should I do?
- We should move this.
- Don't touch it. I'll do it.
- Over there.
- Over here?
Okay.
All right.
(Everything is getting done smoothly.)
(All that's left is the pasta.)
(Is the pasta that's been causing trouble finally cooked?)
(She tries a strand.)
(How is it?)
We just need to cook it in the sauce.
The noodles are cooked.
- Are they cooked?
- Yes.
- Then we're good.
- Right?
- We need to cook it in the sauce.
(From this point, it's a race against the clock.)
(Finally pouring the pasta into the sauce)
- Aren't we done?
- Once pasta is in, we're done.
This is good.
(Cooking the pasta longer while mixing with the sauce)
- I'll serve this much first.
- With the broth.
(Braised pork ribs are ready to be served.)
- It's done.
- Got it.
We're confident now that braised ribs are ready.
- They can also eat pasta.
- Good.
This is good.
I think it's all cooked.
(Portioning the pasta quickly)
Gosh, look at the pasta.
(Pasta is also ready to be served.)
- It looks delicious.
- We're done.
(What is the current time?)
- It's 5:23pm.
- We did it so fast. We're done.
- We finished setting everything up.
- I want to taste it.
(They're ready 7 minutes before serving.)
They can come now.
- I feel so proud.
- I was scared.
(We made it.)
You Seok.
Well done. You did a good job.
- Suddenly, I feel proud.
- It looks beautiful.
- We did it!
- We're ready now.
(Savory braised pork ribs made with love)
(Pasta in tangy tomato sauce)
(Crispy and moist zucchini jeon)
(Kkakdugi, the best side dish with rice)
(Seaweed soup made with wild rock seaweed the siblings harvested)
(Yakbab that elders would love)
(There's even watermelon as a refreshing dessert.)
(A meal prepared by the siblings for the elders)
(We're ready to receive the guests.)
We're ready to receive the guests.
(The siblings standing at the serving station)
- I feel nervous.
- Why do I feel nervous?
Since the guests aren't here yet,
- I'm waiting for them.
- Okay.
I feel nervous.
Why aren't they here yet?
They're coming...
- while holding hands.
- Really?
We're on our way.
(The seniors arrive together.)
(Anticipating)
(The first guests are entering.)
- Oh, my.
- It's starting now.
(We're number 1.)
- Welcome.
- Hello.
(Peeking out to welcome the guests)
(Everyone goes into meerkat mode.)
(Once the seniors are settled in)
- Can we serve the seniors?
- Yes.
- Yes, please come and get food.
- Hello.
Please help yourselves.
Take your time. Enjoy your food.
(The serving officially starts.)
I've been fasting since yesterday to enjoy this meal.
- My goodness.
- Since yesterday?
You must be hungry.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
- It looks so good.
- It looks delicious.
- Feel free to take a lot.
- It looks good.
It's delicious.
Gosh, what's this? It's pasta.
Yes.
- Gosh, it looks beautiful.
- My goodness.
What is this called?
- It's pasta.
- Pasta?
- Yes, it's pasta.
- Pasta.
It's an Italian noodle dish.
It's a foreign noodle dish.
It's slightly spicy.
It's foreign bibim guksu.
(Zucchini jeon)
(Once you fill your plate with food)
Please enjoy your meal.
(Chef Yum will serve you soup.)
It's made with wild rock seaweed.
It's very delicious. I hope you eat a lot.
Here's some pasta.
- Thank you.
- I'll bring you chopsticks...
and spoons.
I should say thanks for the food. Who made it?
- People over there made it.
- Right.
Please help yourself.
The meat is cooked well...
- and tender.
- Okay.
I can't believe this is happening before I die.
(I can't believe this is happening before I die.)
(Thanks to the sibling cooks, she's happy.)
- What's this?
- I made that yakbab.
- Is it yakbab?
- Yes.
Do you want a plate for watermelon?
(They should also take some watermelon.)
Why don't we put some watermelon on each table?
I don't think there's space on their plates.
(Yoon Seo spots the problem with her sharp eyes.)
Shall I do that?
(She immediately grabs some watermelon.)
I'll serve enough watermelon to each table.
(Setting it out on the table)
Hello. Come this way.
- Hello.
- Please come and eat.
(More guests come in from outside.)
- Help yourselves.
- Thank you.
(The line suddenly gets long.)
We can serve them ourselves.
Sun Young, could you serve them the soup?
(To keep things moving quickly, everyone jumps in to serve.)
My goodness.
- Please enjoy.
We have a lot, so please eat a lot.
Please eat a lot.
- I'll take a lot of rice.
- Yes.
I'll take a lot.
(Serving generously)
Would you like some more?
Is this enough?
Why are you taking so little meat? We have a lot of meat.
Would you like a lot? This is wild rock seaweed.
- Hello. Thank you so much.
- Hello.
You must have worked so hard.
I had a lot of fun.
- Did you have fun?
- Yes.
- I've never done it before.
- It looks delicious.
(She hopes that they'd enjoy the food.)
Please enjoy.
(Soon, the cafeteria is filled with the residents.)
Enjoy your food.
(Will the food suit the village people's tastes?)
(A senior takes a spoonful of the soup.)
The soup tastes good.
(A sip of refreshing soup)
(A bite of wild rock seaweed)
(I need to wet some rice in it.)
The seaweed tastes really good.
- It's wild rock seaweed.
- It's really good.
It can only be harvested for 15 days a year.
(Cute)
- The soup is good.
- I like the soup.
The soup and the pasta are good.
(Tangy foreign noodles that suit their taste)
(Slurping)
(He grabs a perilla leaf...)
(and puts some pasta on it.)
(Even pasta wraps on a whole different level make an appearance.)
(He puts ribs on a perilla leaf.)
(Taking a big bite of the wrap)
(Meat on braised pork ribs falls right off the bone.)
(A bite of the meat)
The meat is really good.
The meat is good.
(Savory braised pork ribs also suit their tastes.)
(Relieved)
What's his name?
- The first one?
- Yes.
It's Ji something.
Feel free to take a lot. We have a lot.
(He seems curious about Jin Hee.)
- The King...
- King Ji...
What is his name?
(They know Jin Hee as King Ji.)
The first person standing in the line.
I can't remember his name.
(King Ji is the topic of conversation again.)
I can't remember.
- Ji Jin Hee.
- Right, it's Ji Jin Hee.
- I knew that.
- He's nice-looking.
(Taking a bite of the jeon)
- The jeon is good.
- Everything tastes good.
I usually don't eat jeon, but this is really good.
- You meant the jeon?
- Right.
- They made jeon beautifully.
- I know.
- Please eat a lot.
- Gosh.
(It's zucchini jeon made by Sun Young...)
(with Ji Jeon Hee)
(Both the shape and the taste are the best.)
(The serving line has finally quieted down.)
- It's right here.
- It's here.
I think everyone is here now.
(Staring)
Everyone is enjoying their food.
I know.
- They really enjoy it.
- This is great.
(The siblings' Eat Together that they prepared with care)
Hurry up and come eat.
(Spreading the word about how delicious it is)
I'm eating right now.
It's really good.
They're good cooks.
(At the sight of them enjoying the food,)
(they breathe a sigh of relief.)
- It feels rewarding.
- I know.
It feels rewarding.
This is fascinating.
I agree.
(Screech)
- May I have some more?
- Of course.
- We have a lot. Eat a lot.
- We have a lot.
(A big welcome for refills)
- You can eat more. We have a lot.
What would you like? More pasta?
- This...
- I'll give you a lot.
This is delicious.
Please eat a lot.
- This is really good too.
- What is it?
- It's zucchini jeon.
- This looks so good.
- Please help yourself.
It's zucchini jeon.
(Well done, Sun Young.)
Please help yourselves.
- What would you like?
- Jeon, please.
How many would you like?
- Two, please. It's so good.
- Two?
Gosh, the jeon is very popular.
I'm so glad that we made jeon.
- I know.
- My gosh.
(Shall I go for a refill?)
What will it be?
She's coming for a refill.
(I love refills.)
- Do you want some kkakdugi?
- Kkakdugi?
- Kkakdugi, please.
- Kkakdugi.
- Kkakdugi is also popular.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your food.
- Enjoy.
(What refill will it be this time?)
What would you like?
- Kkakdugi.
- Kkakdugi?
We have a lot of kkakdugi.
Kkakdugi tastes amazing.
Gosh.
We made it from scratch.
- We made it two days ago.
- Right.
(It's hard to resist getting a refill.)
- Kkakdugi is good too.
- Everything tastes good.
- You had a lot.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Everything is delicious.
You're an amazing cook.
- Really?
- Yes.
I was very worried...
because I've never cooked this much before.
- I see.
- I thought that...
it'd be a disaster.
(They're finishing everything off their plates.)
(Spotless)
(Drinking straight from her bowl)
(The village chief suddenly gets up.)
- Sir.
- Attention, everyone.
The cast of Fresh off the Sea treated us...
to dinner at our village.
Let's give them a round of applause to say thank you.
Thank you.
(Thank you for the delicious food.)
(Thank you for enjoying the food.)
- The food is great.
- Thank you.
I ate as much as Tzuyang today.
You know Tzuyang, the famous big eater?
(But no matter how full I am, I can't resist yakbab.)
(If you're Korean,)
(there's always room for yakbab after a meal.)
Is there anything else they need?
Shall I bring you more watermelon?
Do you want more watermelon?
- I had a lot.
- Did you?
I ate a lot.
- Thank you for the food.
- Did you enjoy it?
- Thank you.
- I'm happy to hear that.
- What would you like more?
- This.
- Shall I pack some for you?
- Yes.
I'll pack some for you.
He went to get some medicine, and he isn't coming.
- Who?
- My youngest child.
- Really?
- I see.
We have a lot of braised ribs.
(Please share it with him.)
- Enjoy.
- Take some more yakbab.
- Goodbye.
Can you bring me two more yakbab?
It's for my husband.
Please give her some yakbab.
Do you want more yakbab?
(Quick little steps)
Share it with your husband. Take this too.
I feel so happy.
It tastes better than my usual meals.
Right.
- Thank you for the food.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Goodbye.
- Take care.
- Please take care.
- Thank you.
- Gosh, thank you.
Thank you.
- I ate a lot.
- The serving was generous.
(The cafeteria that was packed with village people is quiet again.)
- It's our turn to eat.
- Let's eat.
My goodness.
- Enjoy your food.
- You worked so hard, Jung Ah.
- Well done, everyone.
- You all worked hard.
(They start their late dinner.)
(Gosh, this is it.)
(Exhaling)
We really gave it everything.
- We put our whole hearts into it.
- We gave it our all.
- It feels very strange.
- Right?
It was touching to see everyone enjoy the food.
I agree.
But it feels strange too.
How shall I put this?
- It's hard to describe.
- I can't put it into words.
(An indescribable feeling)
- I almost teared up...
- Me too.
when everyone kept thanking us.
I don't usually get emotional like that.
So it wasn't my menopause that made me emotional?
- I got emotional too.
- It was okay to get emotional.
When everyone clapped for us...
Right, when everyone clapped for us.
Everyone else...
- They looked completely fine.
- Right.
I thought, "I'm just going through menopause."
I pretended not to get emotional.
We were all feeling the same.
I thought that I was getting overly emotional.
So it wasn't just menopause after all.
I was so happy to see them enjoy the food.
Seriously.
- The jeon was an excellent choice.
- Seriously.
- Jeon and kkakdugi...
- They were the most popular.
They also liked yakbab very much.
(The siblings finally enjoy the food without worrying.)
Isn't the meat good?
Didn't the seasoning get all the way inside?
I have to pack some kkakdugi. It's very delicious.
- Everyone should take some home.
- Seriously.
(We made it ourselves, and it's really good.)
Equally.
- Hello.
My gosh.
- Yes?
- You cooked a meal for us.
- What did you bring?
- It's nothing big.
It's ripened kimchi made by...
women in the village.
By coming to our village,
you gave these elders...
an experience that they never had in their lives.
- Gosh.
- It will be a memory...
that they will keep for a long time.
- Thank you.
- It'll be the same for us.
Thank you.
- Thank you for the kimchi.
- It's ripened kimchi.
This is very precious.
I feel very grateful.
Thank you so much. I enjoyed the meal.
As I've lived for a long time,
I got something so precious.
I feel happy.
I enjoyed the food. Come back soon.
- Shall we go?
- Let's go.
(It's time for the siblings to return home.)
- Three days flew by.
- It's over.
You look so happy.
- Right?
- Yes.
I feel like I can fly away.
We came here on the first day.
- It's hard to believe.
- It feels like I dreamed it.
It feels like a dream.
(It's time to say goodbye to Maegye Village.)
This place will be unforgettable.
I feel like we dreamed it all.
It was like stepping into a storybook.
- Right?
- Yes.
After cooking a meal for all the village elders,
we went home happily...
- ever after.
- Ever after.
Just like that.
(Is this your first time seeing an entrance like this?)
(Yeosu, paradise for the siblings)
(An unusual man makes his entrance.)
(My charm?)
(My nose is big.)
(Who is the guest with a big nose?)
(Jeong Sang Hun is here, a game-changer at the siblings.)
(But the sweetness in paradise doesn't last long.)
(The singles continue their search for love in the spicy inferno.)
(Warning: Things are about to get spicy.)
(A barrage of flirting as hot as the weather)
(What will be their final choice?)
(Get a grip, this is chili pepper inferno!)
(I just need one sip of cold water.)
(The spiciness of Fresh off the Sea will wake you up.)
Jung Ah passed out.
(Can it even knock someone off their feet?)
(The siblings paint a mural in the village for the first time.)
(Following the art major...)
(who's putting her skills to work)
(They add one brushstroke at a time to their memories.)
(How will the siblings' mural turn out?)